<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Akhil Dhingra</title>
    <link>https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Akhil Dhingra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 10:26:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building an AI-Powered Retail Experience with Delta Lake, Spark, and Databricks</title>
      <link>https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/databricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 10:26:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/databricks/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt from my session at Spark-AI connference at Amsterdam 2019.
Zalando SE is Europe&amp;rsquo;s leading online fashion platform and connects customers, brands and partners. With millions of visitors each month, we have petabytes of purchase, click-stream, product and other data in our data lake. This data is crucial to powering insights on shopper behavior and driving an AI-first strategy to improve site engagement.
Over 7 months ago, Zalando adopted Apache Spark, Delta Lake and Databricks as its de-facto computation platform for analytics and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Vs Buy vs Vendor Managed | My Talk at Product Camp</title>
      <link>https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/my-new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 11:29:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhildhingra.github.io/posts/my-new-post/</guid>
      <description>Solving an internal customer need often requires PMs to choose between Build vs Buy. For platform centric offerings in enterprises like Data Transformation / Machine Learning, there is a third option – Vendor Managed. Within large microservices footprint and complex org structures, much of the initial procurement and product discovery happens with key stakeholders and limited beta users. This somewhat reduces feasibility risk, but increases value and usability risk for end users.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>